You say that's recording now.
Okay, so here is that.
I love the fact here,
I just want to say that that's an update
available,
a new version of the app is ready.
Like I love that that comes up there,
you know. So you refresh it.
Well, I don't know,
I click refresh here now, but...
Okay.
Did you see that I clicked on refresh,
Mhm.
but it didn't disappear or nothing
happened. So you probably want to do that.
Yeah.
If you have that, you know,
like it should refresh and then kind of
either disappear or, you know,
not just be the same as if it doesn't
Yeah, supposed to do this for, yeah.
work. You follow me, right? Okay.
Yeah, yeah, yes.
All right, let me just see. Second,
where's my phone?
And now all accounts have the...
the authentication,
multi-factor authentication,
that will be mandatory for now.
Good.
Yeah,
because it's I realized that it has
actually saved me.
Sometimes I get requests on
authentication. Hey,
since it's like I get scared when I see
that because obviously then somebody
knows my password, you know.
Yes.
But I realized that it is really good to
have. What do you want to do,
bridges or ABC interpreting?
This is up to you,
so because we want to test spreadsheet,
so we can use spreadsheet for any any
account.
Okay.
All right, OK,
so we have here ABC interpreting then,
and then...
Let's go a search inventory.
Okay.
So,
I have something in transit that stuff
devices in transit.
All that is.
Added to inventory assigned to John Doe,
assigned to Major Evans.
Assign to roses.
Around, OK.
All right,
so she would then have to check in that.
Well, let's look at that later.
Let's do what we're supposed to do.
Yeah.
Uh.
And.
Oh, yeah.
Category name, mandatory field.
Okay.
Device name.
Good.
I send you the the.
Spreadsheet.
I use this one as a mug,
so that's 500 items.
Okay.
Okay, perfect.
Serial number, the natural field.
What is that?
So serial number mandatory field unique
per unit, one row per physical device.
What does that mean?
One row per physical device?
That will be for,
because they're gonna extract.
But the word row is what I'm trying to
get to here.
Okay,
now because they're going to just get
that,
they're going to filter sort the
information per serial number.
So you're going to put like a serial
number in one row, the second one,
the other row, so on.
So just to organize the data.
Okay.
But when I read it,
it's unique for each unit,
one row per physical device. A row here,
when I think about this,
is a row in this particular spreadsheet.
Row is a very, you know,
when you work a lot with spreadsheets,
row is the row in the spreadsheet that
you're working with.
So I'm wondering if that's the right word
to use here,
because that was the first thing I
associated with.
And clearly we're talking about a cell,
not a row.
Right.
Okay, well, no,
but it's actually it's actually the row,
Or are you talking?
because it's going to get all the
information in the row,
Or the whole row.
but this one will want to be like a
primary key,
and for that was a one per row,
so if if you have one row per physical,
yeah,
if you are you won't be able to have more
than one serial number.
in one row.
Yes, exactly. Unique per unit.
What you can say is unique per unit.
And this row, that's what it would say.
Okay, okay, yes, it's better, yeah.
So just say unique for this unit and this
row, you know, something like that.
Okay.
Right, and then we have cost,
replacement cost as a number.
Okay, good.
Brand perfects.
Perfect.
Ownership, mandatory fields,
standards on permanent insurance.
Common synonyms are mapped for you.
You don't need to say that.
Okay,
now I can just remove all these sentences.
Just say those store,
store as one of permanent rent sale,
and then you can leave that in the code,
but you don't have to say that,
just delete that, you know,
those three risks.
Okay.
Taxable location. Yep.
Location.
Yes,
you can also say where the unit
physically, where the unit is physically,
that's it. Where the unit is physically.
Okay.
What I'm thinking here also is like it's
the top location.
What happened with the telecation?
Yeah, this is the top location.
Yeah, well, you come to the next here,
the sub-location, so...
Yeah.
That's good.
Okay.
It helps extra info,
extra identifier for this unit as key
value.
OK.
Yeah.
Oh, it didn't, it didn't word that.
It say image URL,
but it's supposed to have only image.
But on URL,
Okay.
because you can insert the image and
they're going to just turn into a base 64
Yeah.
and then just save it like that.
Yes, the image, yeah, the, yeah,
so the image,
you just need to rephrase this, I guess.
Or fix it, OK?
Alright, download templates.
Let's look at it.
So it's the same template as you had
before, right? Yeah. Okay.
And you emailed me something you said.
And yeah.
No,
I just hear from the from the chat from
this this meeting.
All from this chat, OK.
See.
Okay, here we go.
Now, of course, it opens it in a browser.
How great is that? Download.
All right.
Okay, so here we have category,
I would do assessments.
Okay,
have you tried to import this at all?
Yeah.
Yeah, I did.
OK, so it worked.
Yeah, so if you see, you can, if you want,
you can just change image. See,
I just added image in that way,
so in the cell, instead of have the URL,
just add the image from the computer.
Okay, got it.
All right.
Or maybe it's already saved. OK, so then.
And.
Start name of it, inventory templates,
mock.
No.
No, that's the template.
Yeah, hold on.
I will save.
One second.
Five 100 units, is that what it has?
Yeah, 100 units.
You didn't enter all of this yourself,
did you? It's not how to...
Yeah, no, no, no,
I just I use a cloud for that.
Ohh.
See, it's creating the image,
and then if you don't have the location,
see now it's completed the task.
Now you have all the locations and also
Okay, location got added.
Perfect.
the information.
So I think this function is going to be
very,
very useful for clients that have a lot
of...
Absolutely.
A lot of inventory, yes,
the faster way to just create inventory
in the in the in the application.
Exactly. All, this is really good.
Okay.
And also I filter the auctions in the
when you add inventory.
Good.
So you asked me to filter based on the
selection.
Mhm.
The other two auctions filter based on
the first selection.
So let's say that you in brand,
you just select.
Del,
and you gonna get all the the groups or
the category related to to those.
Yeah.
Yeah,
there were 28 tasks from the last meeting
that I knocked out with Claudia.
Good, good, good, good, good. You know,
I can see what you're doing.
Yeah.
You realize that too. It has this, uh,
this reporting functionality.
Yeah, no, no, I love, I love AI,
I love cloud, I love open AI,
so because they make your life.
Exactly.
more easy or easier.
Yeah, you can see the analytics here.
We have 5 licenses actually,
so you can see here.
Oh, that's amazing.
You know.
Cesar spent a bit of money.
Yeah.
I still have that.
I don't want to limit him,
but maybe I should. Yeah,
so here you can see.
He loved the function to, he told me that,
why you didn't use it? You know,
I don't like to just give full control.
I want to be on top of that.
Yeah, what do you mean?
But the option that, slash,
you have many commanders on the cloud,
even you that use a lot for the legal
part.
So, this is a slash legal review contract,
and they're gonna just just analyze your
contract as an.
But I do that. I have done that, yes.
I have done a ton of contracts already.
Yes, that's amazing.
Yes. It really helps. But there are also,
you should know, just be forewarned,
it is good and it gives you thing,
but it does miss things.
And unless you have a very, very in-depth.
knowledge of your business or what it is
that you're doing. There are,
it's not doing a good job.
Like I have used it for customizing
agreements or coming up with better text
and it has helped me a lot,
but it also inserted things that are not
good.
Yeah, you need to be on top, yes.
So unless you know what you're doing,
you know,
Right.
you have to be extremely careful because
it doesn't,
it will only take what it knows and use
that. But you know more.
And the problem is there are things that..
.
doesn't belong there that it adds anyway.
You know, and I ended up, you know,
Okay.
with our contract, I ended up deleting.
20% or they put in, I'd say. And not 20,
maybe 15,
but it's still enough for making it a bad
contract.
Ohh, that's good, yes,
and I have got a lot of hacked up.
So, uh, so...
Correct, and it talks too much many times.
It's like too much.
It doesn't need to have all that,
you know. So sometimes I say to it, okay,
Right.
please take this,
see if you can shorten it up with this
amount of pages. Or I will tell you,
you only have.
Five pages, the only percent this on,
no more.
And, you know,
and then I realized that it becomes more
succinct in its meaning, more focused,
better text,
more refined when you set those types of
limits.
Right, some more limit you have,
so they gonna work better in that space.
Yes, but you also have to, yes.
If you just give it full control,
they just losing it.
Yeah, but it babbles a lot then. You know,
it's a lot of things that you don't need
to have that. And also,
but if you go shorter like that,
you also have to up it.
Like you have to use the highest opus for
to get the really good stuff.
I've noticed there is a difference,
like I use sonnet.
for just stupid things. Yeah, exactly. No,
but it things like, oh,
For everything.
I need you to create a spreadsheet with
this and this and this and this.
That's like an idiot can do that. So boom,
here we go.
But when it's like analyses that I want
to.
that I'm not sure if I'm getting
everything,
then I up it to the highest opus to kind
of like do it that way. So yeah.
Yeah,
that's the way that we're supposed to use
the model.
So use the top for analyze or create a
plan. And once you have a detailed plan,
use the cheapest one, cheapest one,
Yeah.
the model, the cheapest one,
and they just follow this plan and
Yeah.
they're going to do exactly what the plan
is.
And you're going to save a lot of talking.
Yeah, so here you can see,
so here you can see you have used 53,
446 lines this month of cloud code.
Yeah, I use a lot.
Yeah, yeah, and Cesar has used 5,198,
whatever he's working on.
Yeah, I saw.
Ohh.
So because I don't like to use the
command goal, you know,
you can use a slash goal and just tell it
what the goal is.
And they're going to start iterate 1 by 1
until you get that goal.
The problem is they're going to just eat
a lot of token because they're going to
escape.
This not, this is not what he wants,
so let me just redo it, redo it, redo it.
Yeah.
I prefer your beer in time, so no,
that's enough for me.
Move on with the next task.
Yeah.
Correct. No,
that's actually how I do it too. You know,
I...
Yeah, I like it that way too.
And now I'm working,
Cesar just sent me a lease of what we
need for FEMRAP, right? That's the name,
and I have, I work.
Yes, FedRAMP.
All the part that the monitor,
all the service, all the endpoints,
and now we have the dashboard,
a private dashboard for us,
and a public dashboard that you can use
it as a key point for self.
So let me show you. If you have,
let me see.
Yes, you are in the touch.
Let me show you, if we go here,
this right here.
And this will be the public.
So that will be this one.
And he's going to show you how the server
is working.
If we have a service that is down,
if we need to put it back,
Zach Claire.
if we're working on. So that way,
the clients can see, okay,
so that's happened.
That's why this function is not working,
but they're working on that.
And from this,
from our parts of the internal part,
you're going to see this is the dashboard,
all the measure. Okay, so this is living,
it says working well,
you're going to see all the metrics.
If this worked, that it's a...
Working delay functions related to delay,
so you wanna say, okay, this is,
and this is one of the things that they
are required to give you the,
I don't know if a certification or or.
Yes, it's certification.
Yeah,
so this is this is how you need to have
checking all your checking all your all
your function.
What?
No, but that's good, you know, yeah.
That's good.
And that's that's also after I knock out
the 28 tests, I I did this with cloud,
so now I still just knock on all the
leads and be able to get that
certification.
Yeah. What you need to do though, also,
what I was thinking is that we do need to
develop a, you know, Devitrak, Fredrik,
Gustavo, Cesar, whomever, dashboard,
like where we can add new companies,
where we can do
You know,
like for the managers of Devitrak
dashboard.
Correct. Yeah.
It is totally different than the
You know.
dashboard that we have right now.
Correct, correct, correct.
that we can see all the clients,
all the accounts,
Yeah.
how they work with that accounts,
all the data that they use.
Yeah, the stripe data, subscription data,
things like that.
We need to start building that too.
You know, yeah.
Okay.
No, that's good. Yeah, yeah,
I'm gonna talk with Cesar and Yo,
we can just have that point in the month.
But focus on the FedRAMP. FedRAMP,
if we can get FedRAMP, oh my goodness,
that is like just saying like we are the
gold standard.
I could actually sell it to the DC
government only on that.
Oh, that's amazing.
If we have FedRAMP, yeah, FedRAMP is key.
If you can get FedRAMP, oof.
Okay.
Yeah,
that's how Cesar and I are working now.
Just get all the points that we need to
be able to present and get that
Yeah.
certification.
Yeah, uh...
Well, the rest,
that's most of my part for now.
Okay, cool. Yeah, let's, let's,
it was kind of short today.
What are we doing Monday? What's our next?
I don't know what's this I have in mind
to check,
but I'll try to talk with him today and
see what will be the points that we're
going to test.
And if I have something in mind, try to,
Yeah.
if I don't have it done yet,
try to knock out.
Today, to get it ready for for Monday.
Yeah, I was thinking that, you know,
I'm gonna I'm gonna do some some testing
on my own then for schools,
just continue that a little bit and and
you know, make a list if there are issues,
because I I I honestly I I haven't sent
Okay.
the e-mail yet, because I...
I want to make sure that I,
if they respond and schedule a time for
demo,
that it cannot have any screw ups then.
I have to be ready.
So it's got to be running like water.
I mean,
within the demo frame of what it is that
we want to demo, right?
So I'm going to do that.
I'm going to do some over the weekend
here,
so see if I can kind of like get to that
point where we're, you know,
or give you more feedback.
But I cannot sit in a room and have a
presentation that is going sideways. So,
and the system has to sell itself.
That's the way to do it.
Okay, yeah, that's the point.
Because that's, you know, yeah,
because then that's credibility, you know,
you know.
Yep.
I told you about the the there was this
this company called.
What the heck? Del Tech.
Del Tech specializes in federal
government research and federal
government opportunities,
and they have a premium accounting system
called Cost Plus.
They also developed a CRM system,
customer relationship management,
just like Salesforce, et cetera.
And they were going to,
they want us to buy it. So I said, okay,
I'll do a demo.
I was interesting because I'm always
interested in, you know, something good.
And we paid too much for sales before.
So I kind of like canceled that.
Turns out that, you know,
when they did the presentation,
I felt it was a little bit clunky and I
realized, like,
this is not going to work for us.
And then the last question I had for them
is like, okay, that's cool.
So do you use this yourself for like me
on our relationship?
And obviously,
it's kudos to them because they didn't
lie, but they say, no, we use Salesforce.
I was just like, what?
Yeah.
Why should I buy your system then?
Why should I just get Salesforce?
Because that's what you're using.
And I was just like,
Exactly.
this is the dumbest thing ever.
So I was just like,
Yeah,
why when I wanna buy this product that
Exactly, what a, exactly. So, but exactly,
but that's the point is like you have to
you don't use it?
Hey,
you're using the product and refusing
right now to use.
be wowed by your own system.
If you are not wowed,
if you don't believe in your own system,
why should I?
Why are you selling it to me?
Go home instead, do something else,
Right.
you know?
Correct. Yeah, that's true.
So, so yeah, anyway, all right. Well,
thank you, Gustavo. Um,
I'll see you Monday,
and are you did you send out an invite
for that meeting already?
Uh, Cesar,
Cesar changed because we have a meeting
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah, okay.
today. He just changed it for Monday.
Alright, sounds good.
Okay.
OK, cool. Have a really good weekend.
Take care. Bye.
What Cesar?
You too. Bye.